Guide to the Brooklyn periodical illustrations BCMS.0003
Brooklyn Collection
- Wars: Revolutionary War
  - The "Old Jersey" Prison Ship. Stiles, History of Kings County, 1884 (Box 6)
- Weather
  - The "Cold Snap" in 1862—Ice in the East River. Harper's Weekly, 1862 February 8 (Box 6)
  - Crossing from Brooklyn to New York on the Ice. Gleason's Pictorial Drawing Room Companion, undated. (Box 6)
  - Crossing the East River on the Ice Bridge. Harper's Weekly, 1871-03-04 (Box 6)
  - Destruction of the Marine Barracks, Brooklyn Navy-Yard, by the Cyclone of January 9th. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1889-01-19 (Box 6)
  - Ice Bridge Across the East River – Rescue of Persons on the Broken Ice. Harper's Weekly, 1867-02-09 (Box 6)
  - The Protracted and Fatal Heated Term In and Around New York City. Harper's Weekly, undated. (Box 6)
  - Scenes and Incidents of the Great Storm of March 12th-13th in and Around New York City. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1888-03-24 (Box 6)
  - A Wet Day on the East River Bridge. Harper's Weekly, 1887-11-05 (Box 6)
- Williamsburg
  - Distillery and Swill Cow Stables On Flushing Avenue and South Second Street. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1858 July 3 (Box 6)
  - Fountain Situated in Eastern District of City of Brooklyn. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1859-05-14 (Box 6)
  - Funeral of the conspirator cook in Williamsburg, Tuesday, Dec 20 – from a sketch by our own artist., 1859 (Box 6)
  - John C. Cool's in Williamsburg [German language]. Frank Leslie's Illustrierte Zeitung, 1859 (Box 6)
  - Ruins of Havemeyer & Elder's Sugar Refinery, Williamsburg. Harper's Weekly, 1882-01-21 (Box 6)
  - The Williamsburg Savings Bank, George B. Post, Architect., 1874 (Box 6)